Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Subject file, 1899-1953; Series IV
  - Council"s Committee on Publications
    - Asakawa, K., 1921-1929 (Box 281, Folder 97)
    - Bacon, Benjamin W., 1916-1931 (Box 281, Folder 98)
    - Bacon, Theodore D., 1924 (Box 281, Folder 98)
    - Bailey, William B., 1918 (Box 281, Folder 98)
    - Bainton, Roland N., 1923-1933 (Box 281, Folder 98)
    - Baker, George P., 1926-1927 (Box 281, Folder 99)
    - Bakewell, Charles M., 1911-1920 (Box 281, Folder 99)
    - Bakke, E. Wright, 1937-1938 (Box 281, Folder 99)
    - Baldwin, Arthur D., 1931-1932 (Box 281, Folder 99)
    - Baldwin, Simeon E., 1918-1919 (Box 281, Folder 100)
    - Bancroft, Frederic, 1924 (Box 281, Folder 100)
    - Barnes, Harry E., 1918-1925 (Box 281, Folder 100)
    - Barnes, Irston R., 1931 (Box 281, Folder 100)
    - Barr, Charles J., 1917 (Box 281, Folder 101)
    - Bartlett, Miss, 1921 (Box 281, Folder 101)
    - Bassett, Samuel E., 1930-1931 (Box 281, Folder 101)
    - Baur, Paul V., 1921-1927 (Box 281, Folder 101)
    - Bayne-Jones, Stahope, 1928-1935 (Box 281, Folder 102)
    - Becker, Carl, 1922 (Box 281, Folder 102)
    - Beers, Henry A., 1917-1926 (Box 281, Folder 103)
    - Bellinger, Arthur R., 1925-1931 (Box 281, Folder 104)
    - Bemis, Samuel, 1936 (Box 281, Folder 104)
    - Benet, Steven V., 1933-1936 (Box 281, Folder 104)
    - Benet, William R., 1923-1930 (Box 281, Folder 104)
    - Bennett, Charles A. A., 1918-1929 (Box 281, Folder 105)
    - Benson, Adolph B., 1929-1930 (Box 281, Folder 106)
    - Berden, John M., 1918-1930 (Box 281, Folder 106)
    - Bidewell, Percy W., 1919-1920 (Box 281, Folder 106)
    - Bingham, Hiram, 1929 (Box 281, Folder 106)
    - Bishop, Allard L., 1919-1930 (Box 281, Folder 107)
    - Bishop, Lottie G., 1927 (Box 281, Folder 108)
    - Blumer, George, 1918-1919 (Box 281, Folder 108)
    - Boltwood, Bertram B., 1918 (Box 281, Folder 108)
    - Borchard, Edwin M., 1919-1934 (Box 281, Folder 109)
    - Bosworth, Edward I., 1924 (Box 281, Folder 110)
    - Bowman, Isiah, 1928-1931 (Box 281, Folder 110)
    - Bradford, Arthur H., 1931 (Box 281, Folder 110)
    - Breasted, James H., 1921 (Box 281, Folder 110)
    - Breckenridge, Lester P., 1920 (Box 281, Folder 111)
    - Brigham, Edwin H., 1924 (Box 281, Folder 111)
    - Brook, Arthur H., 1923 (Box 281, Folder 111)
    - Brooke, C.F. Tucker, 1917-1936 (Box 281, Folder 112)
    - Brown, Charles R., 1918-1926 (Box 281, Folder 113)
    - Brown, Ernest W., 1924-1925 (Box 281, Folder 114)
    - Brown, Lawrason, 1917 (Box 281, Folder 114)
    - Brown, William A., 1917-1922 (Box 281, Folder 114)
    - Buck, Norman S., 1925 (Box 282, Folder 114)
    - Buddhist Art, 1925 (Box 281, Folder 115)
    - Burlingame, Eugene W., 1925 (Box 281, Folder 115)
    - Burr, Harold S., 1924 (Box 281, Folder 115)
    - Bushnell, Samuel C., 1924-1925 (Box 282, Folder 115)
    - Calhoun, Robert L., 1936 (Box 281, Folder 116)
    - Cameron, Edward H., 1919 (Box 281, Folder 116)
    - Canby, Henry S., 1910-1929 (Box 281, Folder 116)
    - Canby, Mrs. Henry S., 1929-1930 (Box 282, Folder 116)
    - Carrington, Fitzroy, 1918 (Box 281, Folder 117)
    - Case, Arthur E., 1925 (Box 281, Folder 117)
    - Caskey, L.D., 1923 (Box 281, Folder 117)
    - Chamberlain, Samuel, 1934 (Box 282, Folder 117)
    - Chittenden, Russell H., 1914-1939 (Box 282, Folder 118)
    - Chronicles of America, 1918-1940 (Box 282, Folder 119)
    - Churchman, John W., 1913-1918 (Box 281, Folder 120)
    - Clapp, Edwin J., 1918 (Box 281, Folder 120)
    - Clark, Charles E., 1931-1934 (Box 282, Folder 120)
    - Clarke, Charles C., 1916-1926 (Box 282, Folder 121)
    - Clay, Albert J., 1915-1924 (Box 282, Folder 122)
    - Coe, Wesley R., 1922-1927 (Box 282, Folder 123)
    - Coffin, Henry S., 1920-1924 (Box 281, Folder 124)
    - Cohen, Morris, 1931 (Box 281, Folder 124)
    - Coker, Francis W., 1918-1938 (Box 281, Folder 124)
    - Coleman, R.V., 1925-1927 (Box 282, Folder 124)
    - Colton, Arthur W., 1927 (Box 282, Folder 125)
    - Conger, George P., 1929 (Box 282, Folder 125)
    - Connecticut Tercentenary, 1934 (Box 282, Folder 125)
    - Constant, Frank H., 1931 (Box 282, Folder 125)
    - Cook, Albert S., 1918-1927 (Box 282, Folder 126)
    - Cook, Walter W., 1926 (Box 282, Folder 126)
    - Corbin, Arthur L., 1921-1939 (Box 282, Folder 127)
    - Corwin, Margaret J., 1916-1917 (Box 282, Folder 127)
    - Corwin, Robert N., 1923-1933 (Box 282, Folder 127)
    - Council"s Committee on publications, 1921-1938 (Box 282, Folder 128-129)
    - Council"s Committee on publications, 1923-1931 (Box 283, Folder 130)
    - Couper, W. J., 1928-1929 (Box 283, Folder 131)
    - Cram, Ralph A., 1917-1921 (Box 283, Folder 131)
    - Crane, T. F., 1918 (Box 283, Folder 131)
    - Crawford, Albert B., 1923 (Box 283, Folder 131)
    - Crawford, Jade R., 1910-1932 (Box 283, Folder 132)
    - Creighton, J.E., 1922 (Box 283, Folder 133)
    - Cross, Wilbur L., 1919-1931 (Box 283, Folder 133)
    - Cumont, Franz, 1921 (Box 283, Folder 134)
    - Cushing, Harvey, 1934 (Box 283, Folder 134)
    - Cutler Lectures, 1921 (Box 283, Folder 134)
    - Dana, Edward S., 1921-1930 (Box 283, Folder 135)
    - Dana, Richard H., Jr., 1924 (Box 283, Folder 135)
    - Dane, Carle H., 1922 (Box 283, Folder 135)
    - Danford, Robert M., 1917-1923 (Box 283, Folder 135)
    - Daniels, Winthrope M., 1929-1933 (Box 283, Folder 136)
    - Darling, Arthur B., 1924-1933 (Box 283, Folder 136)
    - Davenport, Henry, 1920 (Box 283, Folder 136)
    - Davidson, Eugene, 1934-1939 (Box 283, Folder 137)
    - Davie, Maurice, 1924-1927 (Box 283, Folder 138)
    - Davis, Malcolm, 1927-1935 (Box 283, Folder 139-140)
    - Day, Clarence, 1918 (Box 284, Folder 141)
    - Day, Clive, 1918-1938 (Box 284, Folder 141)
    - Day, Frank M., 1917 (Box 284, Folder 141)
    - Day, George P., 1918-1927 (Box 284, Folder 142-143)
    - Dean, Alexander, 1932 (Box 284, Folder 144)
    - Deane, Miss H.G., 1927-1931 (Box 284, Folder 144)
    - Delaguna, Grace A., 1927 (Box 284, Folder 144)
    - Denison, Robert C., 1917-1920 (Box 284, Folder 145)
    - Deuker, Carl G., 1925 (Box 284, Folder 145)
    - DeVane, William C., 1930-1933 (Box 284, Folder 146)
    - Devinne, Theodore L., 1923 (Box 284, Folder 147)
    - Dimnet, Abbe, 1917 (Box 284, Folder 147)
    - Dinsmore, Charles A., 1922 (Box 284, Folder 147)
    - Dixon, Roland B., 1923-1927 (Box 284, Folder 147)
    - Dodd, Lee Wilson, 1923 (Box 284, Folder 148)
    - Dodd, William E., 1924 (Box 284, Folder 148)
    - Donaldson, Norman V., 1928-1938 (Box 284, Folder 149)
    - Dougherty, E.P., 1928-1930 (Box 284, Folder 150)
    - Downes, John I.H., 1917 (Box 284, Folder 150)
    - Dudley, Samuel W., 1929 (Box 284, Folder 150)
    - Dunn, Joseph, 1921-1923 (Box 284, Folder 150)
    - Durham, William H., 1918 (Box 284, Folder 150)
    - Eaton, George F., 1919 (Box 284, Folder 151)
    - Eberhard, Robert G., 1927-1929 (Box 284, Folder 151)
    - Edgerton, Franklin, 1930-1938 (Box 284, Folder 151)
    - Ely, Richard J., 1919 (Box 284, Folder 151)
    - Emkree, Edwin, 1929 (Box 284, Folder 151)
    - English, Yale Studies in, 1938 (Box 284, Folder 152)
    - Erving, H.W., 1931 (Box 284, Folder 152)
    - Evans, Paul D., 1926 (Box 284, Folder 152)
    - Fairchild, Fred R., 1923 (Box 284, Folder 153)
    - Farnum, Henry W., 1918-1920 (Box 284, Folder 153)
    - Farrand, Max, 1909-1930 (Box 284, Folder 154)
    - Farwell, John V., 1932 (Box 284, Folder 155)
    - Fay, Sidney B., 1932 (Box 284, Folder 155)
    - Ferguson, William S., 1922 (Box 284, Folder 155)
    - Ferris, Harry B., 1920-1924 (Box 284, Folder 155)
    - Feuillerat, Albert F., 1929-1936 (Box 284, Folder 156)
    - Fisher, Irving, 1919-1925 (Box 284, Folder 156)
    - Flint, Joseph M., 1920 (Box 284, Folder 156)
    - Foerster, Norman F., 1929 (Box 284, Folder 156)
    - Follett, Wilson, 1914-1924 (Box 284, Folder 157)
    - Follett, Wilson, 1921-1923 (Box 285, Folder 158-159)
    - Foot, Harry W., 1931 (Box 285, Folder 160)
    - Ford, Worthington C., 1922 (Box 285, Folder 160)
    - French, Robert D., 1922-1928 (Box 285, Folder 161)
    - Fulton, John F., 1931-1935 (Box 285, Folder 161)
    - Furniss, Edgar S., 1923-1937 (Box 285, Folder 162)
    - Gabriel, Ralph H., 1920-1932 (Box 285, Folder 163)
    - Gaelic Authorities, undated (Box 285, Folder 164)
    - Gambrill, Bessie, 1930 (Box 285, Folder 164)
    - Garrison, Fielding H., 1923 (Box 285, Folder 164)
    - Garver, Milton, 1920 (Box 285, Folder 164)
    - Gay, Edwin F., 1930 (Box 285, Folder 164)
    - Gerig, John L., 1921 (Box 285, Folder 165)
    - Gesell, Arnold, 1920-1923 (Box 285, Folder 165)
    - Gibbs, J. Willard, 1933 (Box 285, Folder 165)
    - Gidding, Franklin H., 1924-1925 (Box 285, Folder 165)
    - Glasgow, Robert, 1921 (Box 285, Folder 166)
    - Golder, Frank A., 1928 (Box 285, Folder 166)
    - Gooch, F.A., 1918 (Box 285, Folder 166)
    - Goodell, Thomas D., 1913-1920 (Box 285, Folder 166)
    - Goodenough, Erwin, 1926-1936 (Box 285, Folder 167)
    - Grandgent, Charles H., 1922-1925 (Box 285, Folder 167)
    - Graves, Henry S., 1918-1937 (Box 285, Folder 167)
    - Gray, Louis H., 1923 (Box 285, Folder 168)
    - Green, Leon, 1935 (Box 285, Folder 168)
    - Greene, Belle da Costa, 1919 (Box 285, Folder 168)
    - Greene, Evarts B., 1930 (Box 285, Folder 168)
    - Greenfield, Kent Roberts, 1926-1934 (Box 285, Folder 169)
    - Greenway, James C., 1923 (Box 285, Folder 169)
    - Gregory, Herbert, 1918-1924 (Box 285, Folder 169)
    - Gregory, William K., 1924 (Box 285, Folder 169)
    - Gruener, Gustave, 1919-1925 (Box 285, Folder 170)
    - Grummann, S.E., 1925 (Box 285, Folder 170)
    - Hackett, Byrne, 1910-1922 (Box 285, Folder 171-172)
    - Hackett, Francis, 1923 (Box 285, Folder 173)
    - Hadley, Arthur, 1920-1927 (Box 285, Folder 173)
    - Hadley, Morris, 1933 (Box 285, Folder 173)
    - Hague, Marion, 1930 (Box 285, Folder 173)
    - Ham, Roswell G., 1930 (Box 285, Folder 173)
    - Hamilton, Walton, 1931 (Box 285, Folder 174)
    - Harving, Clarence H., 1921-1926 (Box 285, Folder 174)
    - Harlow, Ralph V., 1926-1929 (Box 285, Folder 174)
    - Harmon, Austin M., 1922-1930 (Box 285, Folder 175)
    - Harrison, Ross G., 1922-1936 (Box 285, Folder 176)
    - Harvey, Samuel C., 1922-1924 (Box 285, Folder 176)
    - Haskins, Charles S., 1917 (Box 285, Folder 176)
    - Hastings, Hudson B., 1928-1935 (Box 286, Folder 177)
    - Havemeyer, Loomis, 1920-1925 (Box 286, Folder 177)
    - Hayes, H.G., 1920 (Box 286, Folder 177)
    - Heald, Kenneth C., 1924-1926 (Box 286, Folder 177)
    - Healy, Kent J., undated (Box 286, Folder 178)
    - Healy, William, 1930 (Box 286, Folder 178)
    - Hemingway, Samuel B., 1920-1930 (Box 286, Folder 178)
    - Henderson, Yandell, 1935 (Box 286, Folder 178)
    - Hendrickson, G.L., 1913-1934 (Box 286, Folder 179)
    - Herr, M., 1920 (Box 286, Folder 179)
    - Herring, Hubert, 1937 (Box 286, Folder 179)
    - Hicks, Frederick C., 1930 (Box 286, Folder 179)
    - Hill, Clyde M., 1929-1937 (Box 286, Folder 180)
    - Hocking, William E., 1920-1931 (Box 286, Folder 180)
    - Hodge, F.W., 1922-1924 (Box 286, Folder 180)
    - Hohfeld, Wesley N., 1918 (Box 286, Folder 181)
    - Holloway, Emory, 1918-1920 (Box 286, Folder 181)
    - Hopkins, E. Washburn, 1918-1931 (Box 286, Folder 181)
    - Hotchkiss, W.E., 1920 (Box 286, Folder 182)
    - Howland, Charles P., 1931-1932 (Box 286, Folder 182)
    - Huntington, Ellsworth, 1921-1927 (Box 286, Folder 182)
    - Ivins, Williams M., Jr., 1923 (Box 286, Folder 183)
    - Jayne, W.A., 1923 (Box 286, Folder 183)
    - Johnson, Allen, 1917-1930 (Box 286, Folder 184)
    - Johnson, Alvin, 1938 (Box 286, Folder 185)
    - Johnson, Frederic B., 1920 (Box 286, Folder 185)
    - Johnson, Treat B., 1919 (Box 286, Folder 185)
    - Johnston, John, 1920-1923 (Box 286, Folder 185)
    - Jones, Mary Cadwalader, 1918-1919 (Box 286, Folder 185)
    - Kahn, Eugene, 1933-1934 (Box 286, Folder 186)
    - Karpovitch, Michael, 1935-1936 (Box 286, Folder 186)
    - Keller, Albert G., 1918-1935 (Box 286, Folder 187)
    - Keller, Deane, 1935-1936 (Box 286, Folder 188)
    - Kelly, Frederick, 1925-1926 (Box 286, Folder 188)
    - Kendall, William S., 1918-1921 (Box 286, Folder 188)
    - Kennedy, E.R., 1918 (Box 286, Folder 188)
    - Kent, Charles F., 1919 (Box 286, Folder 188)
    - Keogh, Andrew, 1920-1929 (Box 286, Folder 189)
    - Keyes, Homer Eaton, 1937 (Box 286, Folder 189)
    - Kimball, Fiske, 1936 (Box 286, Folder 189)
    - Kirkpatrick, J.E., 1923-1924 (Box 286, Folder 189)
    - Kittredge, George L., 1924-1925 (Box 286, Folder 189)
    - Knight, H. Stanley, 1923 (Box 286, Folder 190)
    - Knopf, Adolph, 1928-1934 (Box 286, Folder 190)
    - Kohn, Hans, 1938 (Box 286, Folder 190)
    - Krapp, George P., 1924 (Box 289, Folder 190)
    - Kurtz, J.B., 1924 (Box 289, Folder 190)
    - Labaree, Leonard W., 1934-1937 (Box 289, Folder 191)
    - Ladd, George J., 1918 (Box 289, Folder 191)
    - Ladd, W.P., 1929 (Box 289, Folder 191)
    - Lake, Kinsopp, 1922-1926 (Box 289, Folder 191)
    - Lane, John E., 1918 (Box 289, Folder 191)
    - Lang, Henry P., 1919-1933 (Box 286, Folder 192)
    - Lanman, Charles R., 1924-1928 (Box 286, Folder 193)
    - Lanux, Pierre de, undated (Box 286, Folder 194)
    - Latourette, Kenneth S., 1924-1936 (Box 286, Folder 194)
    - Laurens, Henry, 1924 (Box 286, Folder 194)
    - Learned, H. Barret, 1914 (Box 286, Folder 194)
    - Leatherbee, Brigham [Mrs. Albert J.], 1923 (Box 286, Folder 195)
    - Leonard, Robert W., 1924 (Box 286, Folder 195)
    - Levy, S. Leon, 1924-1925 (Box 287, Folder 195)
    - Lewis, Charlton M., 1917-1923 (Box 287, Folder 196)
    - Lewis, Wilmarth S., 1920-1921 (Box 287, Folder 197)
    - Lipari, Angelo, 1924-1931 (Box 287, Folder 198)
    - Llewellyn, Karl N., 1923-1935 (Box 287, Folder 199)
    - Lohman, Carl A., 1929-1931 (Box 287, Folder 200)
    - Lorenzen, Ernest G., 1918 (Box 287, Folder 200)
    - Lowes, John T., 1920 (Box 287, Folder 200)
    - Lull, Richard S., 1918-1927 (Box 287, Folder 201)
    - Luquiens, Frederick B., 1921-1934 (Box 287, Folder 202)
    - Luquiens, Mrs. Frederick B. [Elizabeth K.], 1925 (Box 287, Folder 202)
    - Lusk, [Graham?], 1915 (Box 287, Folder 202)
    - Luther, C.F., 1931 (Box 287, Folder 203)
    - Lybyer, Albert H., 1930 (Box 287, Folder 203)
    - Lyman, David R., 1925 (Box 287, Folder 203)
    - Lyman, Hart, 1924 (Box 287, Folder 203)
    - McAfee, Helen, 1921-1932 (Box 287, Folder 204)
    - MacCracken, Hanry N., 1921-1925 (Box 287, Folder 205)
    - MacCurdy, George G., 1919-1928 (Box 287, Folder 206)
    - MacIntosh, Douglas C., 1913-1925 (Box 287, Folder 207)
    - McKenzie, Kenneth, 1913-1918 (Box 287, Folder 208)
    - Magan, Francis P., Jr., 1929-1933 (Box 287, Folder 208)
    - Mandell, Max S., 1918 (Box 287, Folder 208)
    - Manning, Frederick J., 1924-1925 (Box 287, Folder 208)
    - Mansfield, Harvey, 1938 (Box 287, Folder 209)
    - March, Harold, 1933 (Box 287, Folder 209)
    - Marley, John, 1925 (Box 287, Folder 209)
    - Marshall, John, 1933 (Box 287, Folder 209)
    - Mason, Lawrence, 1920 (Box 287, Folder 209)
    - Mauer, Oscar, 1938 (Box 287, Folder 210)
    - May, Mark, 1928-1931 (Box 287, Folder 210)
    - Meeks, Everett, 1920-1937 (Box 287, Folder 211)
    - Mendel, Lafayette B., 1918-1924 (Box 287, Folder 212)
    - Mendell, Clarence W., 1920-1937 (Box 287, Folder 212)
    - Menner, Robert J., 1926 (Box 287, Folder 212)
    - Merriam, Charles S., 1919 (Box 287, Folder 212)
    - Merritt, Schuyler, 1924-1925 (Box 287, Folder 213)
    - Miles, Harry R., 1924 (Box 287, Folder 213)
    - Mims, Steward L., 1918-1924 (Box 287, Folder 213)
    - Mitchell, Sydney R., 1919-1923 (Box 287, Folder 213)
    - Moore, John B., 1925 (Box 287, Folder 214)
    - Morgan, Edmund M., 1925-1935 (Box 287, Folder 214)
    - Morgan, John Hill, 1928 (Box 287, Folder 214)
    - Morison, Samuel E., 1924 (Box 287, Folder 214)
    - Morris, Elizabeth Woodbridge [Mrs. Charles G.], 1918-1932 (Box 287, Folder 215)
    - Morris, Edward P., 1919-1930 (Box 287, Folder 216)
    - Morris, Francis, 1930 (Box 287, Folder 217)
    - Morris, Ray, 1919 (Box 287, Folder 217)
    - Moseley, Nicholas, 1926 (Box 287, Folder 217)
    - Municipal, 1919 (Box 287, Folder 217)
    - Murdock, George P., 1937 (Box 287, Folder 217)
    - Nagel, Charles, 1931 (Box 287, Folder 218)
    - Neilson, William A., 1921-1923 (Box 287, Folder 218)
    - Nelson, Nels C., 1927 (Box 287, Folder 218)
    - Nemory, Leon, 1925 (Box 287, Folder 218)
    - Nettleton, George H., 1920-1930 (Box 287, Folder 219)
    - Nichols, George E., 1923-1926 (Box 287, Folder 219)
    - Nicoll, Allerdyce, 1936 (Box 287, Folder 219)
    - Northrup, Filmer S.C., 1926-1932 (Box 287, Folder 219)
    - Notestein, Wallace, 1929-1936 (Box 287, Folder 220)
    - Noyes, Edward S., 1923-1924 (Box 287, Folder 220)
    - Oberholtzer, Ellish P., 1922 (Box 287, Folder 221)
    - O"Brien-Moore, A., 1936 (Box 287, Folder 221)
    - Osborn, A., 1920 (Box 287, Folder 221)
    - Osborne, Thomas B., 1927 (Box 287, Folder 221)
    - Oxford, undated (Box 287, Folder 221)
    - Page, Leigh, 1921-1922 (Box 287, Folder 222)
    - Palmer, Arthur H., 1918 (Box 287, Folder 222)
    - Paradise, Burton, 1931 (Box 287, Folder 222)
    - Park, Avery, 1927 (Box 287, Folder 222)
    - Parsons, Francis, 1930 (Box 287, Folder 222)
    - Paton, Stewart, 1926-1928 (Box 287, Folder 223)
    - Pegram, George B., 1931 (Box 287, Folder 223)
    - Percy, William A., 1925-1932 (Box 287, Folder 223)
    - Perrin, Bernadette, 1919 (Box 287, Folder 223)
    - Perry, Bliss, 1920-1922 (Box 287, Folder 223)
    - Petrunkevitch, Alexander, 1917-1933 (Box 287, Folder 224)
    - Phelps, William L., 1918-1933 (Box 287, Folder 225)
    - Phillips, Ulrich B., 1924-1928 (Box 287, Folder 226)
    - Phonetics, 1924 (Box 287, Folder 226)
    - Pierce, Frederick E., 1918-1931 (Box 287, Folder 227)
    - Pirsson, Louis V., 1919 (Box 288, Folder 228)
    - Porter, A. Kingsley, 1917 (Box 288, Folder 228)
    - Potter, Albert K., 1918 (Box 288, Folder 228)
    - Pottle, Frederick A., 1929 (Box 288, Folder 228)
    - Pound, Roscoe, 1935 (Box 288, Folder 228)
    - Putnam, Emily James, 1917 (Box 288, Folder 229)
    - Quaife, M.M., 1924-1926 (Box 288, Folder 229)
    - Rajma, Pio, 1918 (Box 288, Folder 229)
    - Redlick, O., 1930 (Box 288, Folder 229)
    - Reed, Edward B., 1917-1931 (Box 288, Folder 230)
    - Richards, Oscar W., 1935 (Box 288, Folder 231)
    - Richardson, Horace K., 1930 (Box 288, Folder 231)
    - Ripley, Alfred L., 1924 (Box 288, Folder 231)
    - Robinson, Benjamin, 1924 (Box 288, Folder 231)
    - Robinson, Edward, 1927-1930 (Box 288, Folder 231)
    - Robinson, Fred N., 1921-1923 (Box 288, Folder 232)
    - Roe, Joseph W., 1920 (Box 288, Folder 232)
    - Rogers, A.K., 1919 (Box 288, Folder 232)
    - Rogers, Bruce, 1923 (Box 288, Folder 232)
    - Root, Edwin P., 1917 (Box 288, Folder 232)
    - Rose, R. Seldom, 1923-1933 (Box 288, Folder 233)
    - Rostovtzeff, M.I., 1928-1936 (Box 288, Folder 233)
    - Russell, George, 1921 (Box 288, Folder 233)
    - Salmon, Thomas W., 1923 (Box 288, Folder 234)
    - Sanderson, Robert L., 1917-1918 (Box 288, Folder 234)
    - Sapir, Edward, 1932 (Box 288, Folder 234)
    - Savon, O. Glenn, 1931-1932 (Box 288, Folder 234)
    - Schaff, Norman, 1932 (Box 288, Folder 235)
    - Schelling, Felix E., 1930 (Box 288, Folder 235)
    - Schesinger, A.M., undated (Box 288, Folder 235)
    - Schlesinger, Frank, 1922-1936 (Box 288, Folder 235)
    - Schuchert, Charles, 1922-1924 (Box 288, Folder 236)
    - Schreiber, Carl F., 1930-1936 (Box 288, Folder 236)
    - Scott, Ernest F., 1922 (Box 288, Folder 236)
    - Sedgwick, Henry D., 1918 (Box 288, Folder 236)
    - Seronde, Joseph, 1920-1926 (Box 288, Folder 236)
    - Seymour, Charles, 1919-1936 (Box 288, Folder 237)
    - Seymour, George D., 1924 (Box 288, Folder 238)
    - Sheldon, Willmon H., 1920-1937 (Box 288, Folder 238)
    - Shotwell, James T., 1917-1935 (Box 288, Folder 239)
    - Shufeldt, R.W., 1924 (Box 288, Folder 239)
    - Silliman Lectures, 1938 (Box 288, Folder 239)
    - Sills, Kenneth C.M., 1918-1919 (Box 288, Folder 239)
    - Sizer, Theodore, 1933 (Box 288, Folder 240)
    - Smith, C.H., 1909 (Box 288, Folder 240)
    - Smith, David S., 1920-1923 (Box 288, Folder 240)
    - Smith, Elliott D., 1923-1931 (Box 288, Folder 240)
    - Smith, George H., 1920 (Box 288, Folder 240)
    - Smith, Percy, 1919-1921 (Box 288, Folder 241)
    - Smyth, Newman, 1919 (Box 288, Folder 241)
    - Sneath, E. Hershey, 1918-1920 (Box 288, Folder 241)
    - Sorokin, Pitirim A., 1935 (Box 288, Folder 241)
    - Soule, L.P., 1925-1927 (Box 288, Folder 242)
    - Spaulding, Frank E., 1924-1932 (Box 288, Folder 243)
    - Speck, William A., 1919-1924 (Box 288, Folder 243)
    - Sperry, E.E., 1924 (Box 288, Folder 243)
    - Spykman, Nicholas J., 1927-1932 (Box 288, Folder 243)
    - Staff, Harris R., 1925-1929 (Box 288, Folder 244)
    - Starkie, Enid, 1939 (Box 288, Folder 244)
    - Stefansson, Vilhjalmar, 1931 (Box 288, Folder 244)
    - Steiner, Walter R., 1930-1934 (Box 288, Folder 244)
    - Stephenson, Nathaniel W., 1922-1926 (Box 288, Folder 244)
    - Stevens, William O., 1923 (Box 288, Folder 245)
    - Stevenson, E.L., 1926 (Box 288, Folder 245)
    - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1925-1927 (Box 288, Folder 246)
    - Sturges, Wesley A., 1925 (Box 288, Folder 247)
    - Sturtevant, Edgar H., 1924-1927 (Box 288, Folder 247)
    - Swain, George F., 1931 (Box 288, Folder 247)
    - Swan, Thomas W., 1917-1926 (Box 288, Folder 247)
    - Swann, W.F.G., 1926 (Box 288, Folder 247)
    - Tarkell, Frank B., 1917-1922 (Box 288, Folder 248)
    - Taylor, Edwin C., 1925-1935 (Box 288, Folder 248)
    - Teggart, Frederick J., 1917-1919 (Box 288, Folder 248)
    - Terry Lectures, 1936-1937 (Box 288, Folder 249)
    - Thalbitzer, William, 1931 (Box 288, Folder 250)
    - Tilden, Charles J., 1921-1924 (Box 288, Folder 250)
    - Tileston, Wilder, 1920 (Box 288, Folder 250)
    - Tinker, Chauncey B., 1919-1937 (Box 288, Folder 251)
    - Torrey, Charles C., 1918-1934 (Box 288, Folder 252)
    - Townsend, Gertrude, 1930 (Box 289, Folder 253)
    - Tracy, John C., 1920 (Box 289, Folder 253)
    - Trowbridge, Mrs. Elford, 1920 (Box 289, Folder 253)
    - Tufts, James H., 1922-1923 (Box 289, Folder 253)
    - Turner, E. Raymond, 1924 (Box 289, Folder 253)
    - Tuttle, Julius H., 1923-1924 (Box 289, Folder 254)
    - Twining, N.C., 1923 (Box 289, Folder 254)
    - Uhler, Horace S., 1924 (Box 289, Folder 254)
    - Underhill, Frank P., 1930 (Box 289, Folder 254)
    - Urban, Wilber M., 1937 (Box 289, Folder 254)
    - Vaughan, Herbert H., 1922-1923 (Box 289, Folder 255)
    - Venturi, Lionello, 1936 (Box 289, Folder 255)
    - Vernadsky, George, 1927-1937 (Box 289, Folder 255)
    - Victoria Letters, 1937 (Box 289, Folder 255)
    - Walker, Williston, 1918-1921 (Box 289, Folder 256)
    - Ward, C.F., undated (Box 289, Folder 256)
    - Waterman, Alan T., 1935 (Box 289, Folder 256)
    - Warren, Charles H., 1927-1931 (Box 289, Folder 256)
    - Warren, Fredrick M., 1919 (Box 289, Folder 257)
    - Webb, Vanderbilt, 1932 (Box 289, Folder 257)
    - Weigand, Hermann J., 1933 (Box 289, Folder 257)
    - Weigle, Luther A., 1922-1929 (Box 289, Folder 257)
    - Weld, L.D.H., 1917 (Box 289, Folder 258)
    - Wells, John E., 1919 (Box 289, Folder 258)
    - Westerfield, Ray B., 1920 (Box 289, Folder 258)
    - Whelden, C.H., Jr., 1931 (Box 289, Folder 258)
    - Wilder, Thorton, 1933 (Box 289, Folder 259)
    - Wilkin, Robert N., 1938 (Box 289, Folder 259)
    - Williams, F. Wells, 1918-1926 (Box 289, Folder 259)
    - Williams, Stanley T., 1920-1935 (Box 289, Folder 260)